Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.3.6
Marist College
  Box 1537 - Box 1543
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1541 - Box 1544
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1545 - Box 1548
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1549 - Box 1552
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1553
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 1 (Box 1553)
    - [postcard] Capt. Woolsey in the Detroit; (Photo from Mrs. Woolsey, 1
    - Verso: Capt. Woolsey in the Detroit; (Photo from Mrs. Woolsey, 1-verso
    - Caption: Market, Alright Here, 2
    - Caption: Porto Alegre Brazil, 3
    - [A crowd surrounding an automobile; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 4
    - 9 de Octubre Avenue - The Monuments of October in the background, 5
    - Verso: 9 de Octubre Avenue - The Monuments of October in the background, 5-verso
    - The statue of Simon Bolivar, Guayaquil., 6
    - Verso: The statue of Simon Bolivar, Guayaquil., 6-verso
    - Bolivar Street - Guayaquil- Ecuador., 7
    - Verso: Bolivar Street - Guayaquil- Ecuador., 7-verso
    - The gardens of the Plaza Bolivar, Guayaquil., 8
    - Verso: The gardens of the Plaza Bolivar, Guayaquil., 8-verso
    - The country near Guayaquil., 9
    - Verso: The country near Guayaquil., 9-verso
    - Railroad station in the Malecon Street. Guayaquil, 10
    - Verso: Railroad station in the Malecon Street. Guayaquil, 10-verso
    - One of the most crowded commercial thoroughfares in town., 11
    - Verso: One of the most crowded commercial thoroughfares in town., 11-verso
    - The most prominent commercial distric of the city, 12
    - Verso: The most prominent commercial distric of the city, 12-verso
    - Luque Street- Guayaquil - Ecuador, S.A., 13
    - Verso: Luque Street- Guayaquil - Ecuador, S.A., 13-verso
    - Guayaquil- Ecuador The old colonial quarters of the city, 14
    - Verso: Guayaquil- Ecuador The old colonial quarters of the city, 14-verso
    - La Merced Church and Pedro Carbo Square. Guayaquil, 15
    - Verso: La Merced Church and Pedro Carbo Square. Guayaquil, 15-verso
    - Picturesque scene in the suburbs of Quito, Ecuador, 16
    - Verso: Picturesque scene in the suburbs of Quito, Ecuador, 16-verso
    - Buenaventura, 17
    - Verso: Buenaventura, 17-verso
    - Buenaventura, 18
    - Verso: Buenaventura, 18-verso
    - The Post Office Building- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 19
    - Verso: The Post Office Building- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 19-verso
    - Boulevard 9 d eOctubre- Guayaquil., 20
    - Verso: Boulevard 9 d eOctubre- Guayaquil., 20-verso
    - Pedro Cardo Street- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 21
    - Verso: Pedro Cardo Street- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 21-verso
    - Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 22
    - Verso: Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 22-verso
    - Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 23
    - Verso: Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 23-verso
    - Caption: El "Detroit" Cap. Woosley Tte. Benton, 24
    - Caption: El "St. Louis" Teniente Tompson Mc. Weddington, 25
    - Caption: El "San Francisco" Cap. Baker Tte. Fairchild, 26
    - Caption: Pedra Redonda (Emergency), 27
    - [Map of plane route from the Pan-American Flight], 28
    - Caption: Porto Alegre, Brazil Waterfront, 29
    - Porto Allegre, Maj. Dargue, 30
    - Verso: Porto Allegre, Maj. Dargue, 30-verso
    - Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 31
    - Verso: Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 31-verso
    - &Plaza Rocafuerte- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 32
    - Verso: &Plaza Rocafuerte- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 32-verso
    - Caption: Vista Panoramica de la Parte este de la Ciudad de Santo Domingo, R.D. Interior del Puerto Ozama. [Panorama of Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic], 33
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 2 (Box 1553)
    - Puerto Cabello, Maj. Dargue, 1
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, Maj. Dargue, 1-verso
    - Puerto Cabello, Maj. Dargue, 2
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, Maj. Dargue, 2-verso
    - [A crowd surrounding an automobile], 3
    - [People standing in a field], 4
    - railroad station in the Malecon Street. Guayaquil, 5
    - [People surrounding the pilots of the Pan-American Flight], 6
    - [Men standing around barrels; taken from the Pan-American Flight], 7
    - Modern buildings in the Malecon of Guayaquil., 8
    - Verso: Modern buildings in the Malecon of Guayaquil., 8-verso
    - Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 9
    - Verso: Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 9-verso
    - Massonic Temple- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 10
    - Verso: Massonic Temple- Guayaquil- Ecuador., 10-verso
    - Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 11
    - Verso: Street Scene- Guayaquil- Ecuador, 11-verso
    - Caption: San Jose C.R - Parque Central - Central Park; Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 12
    - Verso: Return to Mrs. Benton, 12-verso
    - Caption: Puerto de Santa Fe - Republica Argentina, 13
    - Caption: Puerto de Santa Fe - Republica Argentina, 14
    - Caption: El Combustible listo para los Aviones, 15
    - Caption: El S. "New York" Mayor Dargue Tte. Whishouse, 16
    - Caption: El "San Antonio" Amarlzando Cap. McDaniel Tte. Robinson, 17
    - Caption: Puerto de Paita; Verso: This shows the cnhorage of the numberous small boats..., 18
    - Verso: This shows the cnhorage of the numberous small boats..., 18-verso
    - Maj H.A. Dargue, 19
    - Verso: Maj H.A. Dargue, 19-verso
    - Buenaventura, 20
    - Verso: Buenaventura, 20-verso
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with broadcasters) [includes color photographs], 1930s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1553)
    - Geo. Arkedis, 1
    - Verso: Geo. Arkedis, 1-verso
    - Bill Leonard, 2
    - Verso: Bill Leonard, 2-verso
    - Lowell - for your files, Harry; L to R - Walter Cronkite - Harry A. Bruno - Lowell Thomas - Dr. Thomas O Paine, 3
    - Verso: Lowell - for your files, Harry; L to R - Walter Cronkite - Harry A. Bruno - Lowell Thomas - Dr. Thomas O Paine, 3-verso
    - Left to right: Westbrook Pegler, Lowell Thomas, Frank Mason, Floyd Gibbons (L.T. succeeded Gibbons on NBC, for The Literary Digest, in Sept. 1930); Note: Westbrook Pegler (left) noted columnist, L.T., "Buzz" LaQuotte, Floyd Gibbons; Note: Floyd Gibbons (eye patch) w/ L.T., 4
    - Verso: Left to right: Westbrook Pegler, Lowell Thomas, Frank Mason, Floyd Gibbons (L.T. succeeded Gibbons on NBC, for The Literary Digest, in Sept. 1930), 4-verso
    - Note: Westbrook Pegler (left) noted columnist, L.T., "Buzz" LaQuotte, Floyd Gibbons, 5
    - Note: Floyd Gibbons (eye patch) w/ L.T., 6
    - [copy of photograph 3.4], 7
    - [Walter Cronkite and Lowell Thomas], 8
    - Left to Right: Trout, Goodman, Cole, Thomas, Jackson Kyes, 9
    - Verso: Left to Right: Trout, Goodman, Cole, Thomas, Jackson Kyes, 9-verso
    - Barbara Walters, 10
    - Verso: Barbara Walters, 10-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a woman at a banquet], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table with two others], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table with two others], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a woman], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman at a banquet], 15
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman across the table], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas at a banquet], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two women at a banquet], 18
    - Dallas Townsend of CBS, 19
    - Verso: Dallas Townsend of CBS, 19-verso
    - Harry Reasoner and L.T. IPA conven-, 20
    - Verso: Harry Reasoner and L.T. IPA conven-, 20-verso
    - Harry Reasoner and L.T. IPA conven-, 21
    - Verso: Harry Reasoner and L.T. IPA conven-, 21-verso
    - [Eric Sevareid], 22
    - LT with Eric Sevareid, 23
    - Verso: LT with Eric Sevareid, 23-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man on the air at NBC], 24
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with entertainers), circa 1930s - 1970s; 4 (Box 1553)
    - [Arthur Godfrey and Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with an entertainer], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man while holding "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man while holding his "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man while holding "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man while holding "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man while holding "Lowell Thomas' Book of the High Mountains"], 7
    - Arthur Godfrey [left], 8
    - Verso: Arthur Godfrey [left], 8-verso
    - M/M Art Linkletter, L.T., Bill Lear (Steam Caps, Lear Jets), 9
    - Verso: M/M Art Linkletter, L.T., Bill Lear (Steam Caps, Lear Jets), 9-verso
    - M/M Art Linkletter, L.T., Lear of Lear Jet fame, 10
    - Verso: M/M Art Linkletter, L.T., Lear of Lear Jet fame, 10-verso
    - Thelma Ritter, character actress, and Governor John Love of Colorado on left; March '63, 11
    - Verso: Thelma Ritter, character actress, and Governor John Love of Colorado on left; March'63, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with entertainers], 12
    - [Ann Miller and LT], 13
    - Wendy Barry, 14
    - Verso: Wendy Barry, 14-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to two other entertainers at CBS], 15
    - L. Louis Seltzer, Helen Hayes, 16
    - Verso: L. Louis Seltzer, Helen Hayes, 16-verso
    - [Helen Hayes], 17
    - Caption: See what happened to me since I got my new DELCO battery! Verso: Pat; - What would you suggest for a caption to this historic picture? [Lowell Thomas with Jayne Mansfield], 18
    - Verso: Pat; - What would you suggest for a caption to this historic picture? [Lowell Thomas with Jayne Mansfield], 18-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with an entertainer], 19
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with an entertainer], 20
    - [Dina Merrill]; Verso: Art Linkletter; About to be interrupted?! - 2/14/1973, 21
    - Verso: Art Linkletter; About to be interrupted?! - 2/14/1973, 21-verso
    - [Wendell Corey and Stewart Granger, 1951], 22
    - [Wendell Corey and Stewart Granger, 1951], 23
    - [Wendell Corey and Stewart Granger, 1951], 24
    - Lowell Thomas with Major Bowes, Ed Wynn, Jack Pearl, Paul Whiteman, David Warfield and James Brady, 25
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas with Major Bowes, Ed Wynn, Jack Pearl, Paul Whiteman, David Warfield and James Brady, 25-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with Major Bowes, Ed Wynn, Jack Pearl, Paul Whiteman, David Warfield and James Brady], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with two women at a banquet table], 27
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with foreign statesmen), undated; 5 (Box 1553)
    - L.T. with King Hussein of Jordan, 1
    - Verso: L.T. with King Hussein of Jordan, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at a podium next to King Hussein of Jordan], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at a podium next to King Hussein of Jordan], 3
    - LT, "Red" R[?], President Osmena in [Manila?], 4
    - Verso: LT, "Red" R[?], President Osmena in [Manila?], 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with two soreign statesmen at an ornate desk], 5
    - LT and King Saud?, 6
    - Verso: LT and King Saud?, 6-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a foreign statesman], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a foreign statesman], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a foreign statesman], 9
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with military personnel), 1930s - 1970s; 6 (Box 1553)
    - Including, from l. to r.: - Branch Rickey, Jimmy Walker, Tex O'Rourke, Major General Chennault, Lowell Thomas; Major Jimmy Walker (left), Gen. Claire Chennault of Flying Tiger fame., 1
    - Verso: Including, from l. to r.: - Branch Rickey, Jimmy Walker, Tex O'Rourke, Major General Chennault, Lowell Thomas; Major Jimmy Walker (left), Gen. Claire Chennault of Flying Tiger fame., 1-verso
    - L.T. Jr. and LT Sr. with Admiral George Edwards U.S. Navy - Pacific, 2
    - Verso: L.T. Jr. and LT Sr. with Admiral George Edwards U.S. Navy - Pacific, 2-verso
    - Mrs. Jimmy Doolittle and L.T., 3
    - Verso: Mrs. Jimmy Doolittle and L.T., 3-verso
    - Doolittle [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle], 4
    - Note: Doolittle [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle], 5
    - Mrs. Douglas MacArthur [Jean MacArthur], 6
    - Note: Mrs. Douglas MacArthur [Jean MacArthur], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to an elderly woman], 8
    - L.T. and General Douglas MacArthur, Tokyo H.Q., 9
    - Verso: L.T. and General Douglas MacArthur, Tokyo H.Q., 9-verso
    - shortly before McArthur's death, 10
    - Verso: shortly before McArthur's death, 10-verso
    - Gen. Robt Lee Bullarld, 2nd ranking US Commander in W.W.I, and L.T., 11
    - Verso: Gen. Robt Lee Bullarld, 2nd ranking US Commander in W.W.I, and L.T., 11-verso
    - At Headquarters, Panama Canal Dept., L.T. with Lt. Gen. George H. Brett, Commanding General of the Caribbean Defense Command, just before making an inspection flight over the Canal. Gen. Brett personally piloted the "Swoose", 12
    - Verso: At Headquarters, Panama Canal Dept., L.T. with Lt. Gen. George H. Brett, Commanding General of the Caribbean Defense Command, just before making an inspection flight over the Canal. Gen. Brett personally piloted the "Swoose", 12-verso
    - Lt. Gen. "Bobbie" Burns. Ass't. Chief of Staff, 13
    - Verso: Lt. Gen. "Bobbie" Burns. Ass't. Chief of Staff, 13-verso
    - Next to L.T. World War I Canadian ace shot down over 100 German Planes. His name -, 14
    - Verso: Next to L.T. World War I Canadian ace shot down over 100 German Planes. His name -, 14-verso
    - THE GENERAL AT RINGSIDE: General Douglas MacArthur (center) chats with Eddie Eagan (left) chairman of the New York State Athletic Commission and Gene Tunney, former heavyweight champion at ringside in Yankee Stadium, New York, June 27, before start of Irish Bob Murphy - Jake LaMotta bout. Murphy stopped Jake after seven rounds of hard fighting. 6/28/51, 15
    - Note: THE GENERAL AT RINGSIDE: General Douglas MacArthur (center) chats with Eddie Eagan (left) chairman of the New York State Athletic Commission and Gene Tunney, former heavyweight champion at ringside in Yankee Stadium, New York, June 27, before start of Irish Bob Murphy - Jake LaMotta bout. Murphy stopped Jake after seven rounds of hard fighting. 6/28/51, 16
    - THE GENERAL AT RINGSIDE: General Douglas MacArthur (center) chats with Eddie Eagan (left) chairman of the New York State Athletic Commission and Gene Tunney, former heavyweight champion at ringside in Yankee Stadium, New York, June 27, before start of Irish Bob Murphy - Jake LaMotta bout. Murphy stopped Jake after seven rounds of hard fighting. 6/28/51, 17
    - Main reviewing stand - at the Plaza - American Legion Parade - Sept. 1947; Retiring Commander Colmery on LT's right; Governor of Ohio in civilian clothes on LT's left, 18
    - Verso: Main reviewing stand - at the Plaza - American Legion Parade - Sept. 1947; Retiring Commander Colmery on LT's right; Governor of Ohio in civilian clothes on LT's left, 18-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two military officials], 19
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with political figures), 1930s - 1970s; 7 (Box 1553)
    - Alice Roosevelt Longworth [Lowell Thomas, center, Henry Kissinger, right], 1
    - Verso: Alice Roosevelt Longworth [Lowell Thomas, center, Henry Kissinger, right], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with Alice Roosevelt and Henry Kissinger], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with Alice Roosevelt and Henry Kissinger], 3
    - [Nelson Rockefeller and Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and Nelson Rockefeller], 5
    - [Nelson giving a speech while looking at Lowell Thomas], 6
    - L.T. and Nelson Rockefeller, 7
    - Verso: L.T. and Nelson Rockefeller, 7-verso
    - [Nelson] Rockefeller, LT, Stahlman, [Bernt] Balchen, 8
    - Verso: [Nelson] Rockefeller, LT, Stahlman, [Bernt] Balchen, 8-verso
    - Winthrop Rockefeller, LT, Nelson Rockefeller, 9
    - Verso: Winthrop Rockefeller, LT, Nelson Rockefeller, 9-verso
    - Roger Blough, Ch. Of Bid of U.S. Steel, L.T., and Gov. [Governor Nelson] Rockefeller, 10
    - Verso: Roger Blough, Ch. Of Bid of U.S. Steel, L.T., and Gov. [Governor Nelson] Rockefeller, 10-verso
    - [Nelson Rockefeller, left, Lowell Thomas, second from left], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Nelson Rockefeller, right], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas, center, Nelson Rockefeller, right], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas with Barry Goldwater], 14
    - Lowell Thomas, General James Doolittle, Senator Barry Goldwater, General R.A. Knobloch, 15
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, General James Doolittle, Senator Barry Goldwater, General R.A. Knobloch, 15-verso
    - One of my better pictures: The Listener [Spiro Agnew at right], 16
    - Verso: One of my better pictures: The Listener [Spiro Agnew at right], 16-verso
    - LT Jr., Dr. Howard Rusk, LT Sr., 17
    - Verso: LT Jr., Dr. Howard Rusk, LT Sr., 17-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men at a banquet], 18
    - ?, Pres. Hoover and LT, 19
    - Verso: ?, Pres. Hoover and LT, 19-verso
    - LT and Mayor LaGuardia., 20
    - Verso: LT and Mayor LaGuardia., 20-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and Senator John Tower., 21
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas and Senator John Tower., 21-verso
  - Subject files: Personalities (Lowell Thomas with sports figures), 1940s - circa 1978; 8 (Box 1553)
    - Jack Dempsey, 1
    - Verso: Jack Dempsey, 1-verso
    - [Jack Dempsey], 2
    - Caption: Lowell you are the real champ -Hugh [LT, Hugh O Brien, Muhammed Ali] [Mrs. Marianna Thomas, right, circa 1978], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with Hugh O'Brien and Muhammed Ali]], 4
    - [Robert] Ripley and Babe Ruth, 5
    - Verso: [Robert] Ripley and Babe Ruth, 5-verso
    - Bob Feller, on LT's left, 6
    - Verso: Bob Feller, on LT's left, 6-verso
    - TAKES BIG TRIP TO SEE DODGERS; Having traveled nearly half way around the world to see his first professional baseball game and to study American sports, Abd Traboulsi, Director of Athletics at the American University of Beirut, Lebanon, was the guest of Branch Rickey June 20 when the Brooklyn Dodgers defeated the Pittsburgh Pirates. Other guests at the game were Commissioner "Happy" Chandler and Ford Frick, President of the National League. Mr. Traboulsi who hopes eventually to introduce American baseball to his native Lebanon, plans to spend the summer at Ann Arbor taking a course for physical directors at the University of Michigan. With the American University of Beirut for 20 years, Mr. Traboulsi has charge of the athletic program for 2500 students representing 40 nationalities comprising the largest American university overseas. The American University of Beirut is a member of the Near East College Association of which Lowell Thomas is National Chairman and Allen Dulles, President of the Board of Directors. Photo shows: (left to right: Red Barber, Mr. Traboulsi, Commissioner Chandler and Mr. Rickey, 7
    - Note: TAKES BIG TRIP TO SEE DODGERS; Having traveled nearly half way around the world to see his first professional baseball game and to study American sports, Abd Traboulsi, Director of Athletics at the American University of Beirut, Lebanon, was the guest of Branch Rickey June 20 when the Brooklyn Dodgers defeated the Pittsburgh Pirates. Other guests at the game were Commissioner "Happy" Chandler and Ford Frick, President of the National League. Mr. Traboulsi who hopes eventually to introduce American baseball to his native Lebanon, plans to spend the summer at Ann Arbor taking a course for physical directors at the University of Michigan. With the American University of Beirut for 20 years, Mr. Traboulsi has charge of the athletic program for 2500 students representing 40 nationalities comprising the largest American university overseas. The American University of Beirut is a member of the Near East College Association of which Lowell Thomas is National Chairman and Allen Dulles, President of the Board of Directors. Photo shows: (left to right: Red Barber, Mr. Traboulsi, Commissioner Chandler and Mr. Rickey, 8
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1940s - circa 1978; 9 (Box 1553)
    - Admiral Halsey? and LT, 1
    - Verso: Admiral Halsey? and LT, 1-verso
    - ? and LT, 2
    - Verso: ? and LT, 2-verso
    - ? LT, 3
    - Verso: ? LT, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with President of Protor & Gamble], 4
    - LT, Pres of P &G, 5
    - Verso: LT, Pres of P &G, 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with President of Protor & Gamble], 6
    - LT and ?, 7
    - Verso: LT and ?, 7-verso
    - ?, LT, 8
    - Verso: ?, LT, 8-verso
    - LT, Mrs. T and ?, 9
    - Verso: LT, Mrs. T and ?, 9-verso
    - Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, 10
    - Verso: Sir Wilfred Grenfell and LT, 10-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and David O. McKay], 11
    - [Newspaper clipping discussing Lowell Thomas and President David O McKay] [PDF], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man looking at a book], 13
    - Caption: To my pal Lowell Thomas! A #1 Guy Best Wishes Enthusiastically, [signed] Joe [Girard]; Note: put his picture in famous file ..., 14
    - Note: put his picture in famous file ..., 15
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with three other men], 16
  Box 1554
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Personalities, circa 1940s - 1970s; 1 (Box 1554)
    - Former Univ. of Mich. All-American football star Neumann, Poet Edgar Guest, George "Dick" Richards, WJR - etc., LT, 1
    - Verso: Former Univ. of Mich. All-American football star Neumann, Poet Edgar Guest, George "Dick" Richards, WJR - etc., LT, 1-verso
    - LT Jr., ?, LT Sr., 2
    - Verso: LT Jr., ?, LT Sr., 2-verso
    - Donald Douglas - center; He and LT born same day. Same age Apr. 6, 1892; Lt. Jack Harding - First World Flight, 3
    - Verso: Donald Douglas - center; He and LT born same day. Same age Apr. 6, 1892; Lt. Jack Harding - First World Flight, 3-verso
    - M/M Samuel Pryor, woman may be Kay Fanning, and LT in Alaska, 4
    - Verso: M/M Samuel Pryor, woman may be Kay Fanning, and LT in Alaska, 4-verso
    - Charles E Murphy, Osa Johnson, and LT, 5
    - Verso: Charles E Murphy, Osa Johnson, and LT, 5-verso
    - Col. Howard Rusk, LT and ?, 6
    - Verso: Col. Howard Rusk, LT and ?, 6-verso
    - A group of his pals greeted him when he returned to Cripple Creek. His right hand is on the shoulder of Cripple Creek Postmaster Danny Sullivan who "saved TR's [Theodore Roosevelt's] life" in 1900 when an assassin was about to kill him. 3rd from left Colorado's Governor Ralph Carr, 7
    - Verso: A group of his pals greeted him when he returned to Cripple Creek. His right hand is on the shoulder of Cripple Creek Postmaster Danny Sullivan who "saved TR's [Theodore Roosevelt's] life" in 1900 when an assassin was about to kill him. 3rd from left Colorado's Governor Ralph Carr, 7-verso
    - To Lowell Thomas from old friends and admirers. The Red Motleys, 8
    - Note: To Lowell Thomas from old friends and admirers. The Red Motleys, 9
    - Caption: G. A. Richard's All-American 59th Birthday Party; March 19, 1948; Lowell Thomas, Captain Eddie Rickenbacker, Sid Luckman, Bo McMillan, Coach, G. A. Richards, Ernie McCoy, Ty Cobb, Frank Leahy, Father Cavanaugh, Pres. John A. Hannah, Gov. Kim Sigler, George Halas, 10
    - Dinner in Detroit in honor of Mr. George "Dick" Richards, owner of Station WJR, In the Picture: Capt. Eddie Rickenbacker, Football Star Sid Luckman (standing) Governor Kim Ziegler, wearing glasses, 11
    - Verso: Dinner in Detroit in honor of Mr. George "Dick" Richards, owner of Station WJR, In the Picture: Capt. Eddie Rickenbacker, Football Star Sid Luckman (standing) Governor Kim Ziegler, wearing glasses, 11-verso
    - [with letter to Lowell Thomas from Carl Karcher concerning photograph], 12
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Carl Karcher concerning photograph] [PDF], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a conference table with other men including Admiral Dick Bird and Theodore Roosevelt, Jr.], 14
    - Note: [Flexograph sleave] 9/13/46 Lowell Thomas Radio Broadcast, 15